hello my name is green and i'm about to
steal my own door to stop suspicion in
my direction people are starting to
notice that their doors are missing i
just need i need to start storing this
better we'll come back to this because
it is nearly 5 p.m for the head hunt
game to begin now i want to capitalize
on this by submitting the heads
immediately i have got a corrales i've
got three paralysis that i got from a
wandering trader and i got a good times
with scar head from um disastrous means
so i can be the first one to get the
points for these heads if i get there in
the next three minutes doesn't look like
anybody's there the game is just minutes
away from starting i'm just gonna wait
here
until it's time to go
four minutes
oh
zeraph is there maybe he's got the same
idea as me
not entirely sure i hope he hasn't got
the same heads that i do
he's heading in that direction don't be
cleo's there pvp starts in three minutes
now do i just go and submit these heads
as fast as possible fly in and fly out
or do i try and get zeddaf's head
oh i think he's like a i think he might
be a last minute entry i don't even know
if he's in the game yet you've got two
minutes to sign up zf two minutes
there's
just so many last minute sign ups i need
to be careful here i'm a little bit
nervous
i'm a little bit nervous i'm not even
sure how many people have signed up to
tag to electric boogaloo but if they
kill me they don't get the tag unless
they've paid up that i mean that's
obvious you're only in the game if you
paid your diamonds one minute soon
this is so cheeky gotta get in there
quick if i want these points and it has
just ticked over to five o'clock go go
go go go go go go go
where is corrales
corrales corrales corrales isco mumbo
tango zuma oh there is
bop bop bop where's good times with scar
am i blind where is scars
oh there it is scar boom no no
i secured my points i've got i've got
too much to live for cleo's the only one
that's actually started
how did green get three corrales heads
already
[Laughter]
there's no point in me getting corrales
because
i've already submitted the three
corrales heads i've got max points on
that and i got 10 points four for scars
as well well zedf is here you can kill
him it's not a safe place do i risk it
if i let them fight fight him fight him
i'll go for it i'll going for it he's
that up
diesel
no
get back here
hey
we got him we got him i'll put i'll pop
his stuff in a shulker box oh man
where's all his stuff i'll leave he's
got oh he's got so many mob heads i'll
leave all these these are his these are
his i'm not gonna steal anything other
than the head that i've got from him i
think that's all his stuff okay i think
he's good you can have the shulker box
where's zf's
my heart's going i don't like this
zf
bing oh i need to rename it korean and
we secure another 10 points
yay
right let's get ourselves somewhere safe
and so we could tell tell zeddaff i just
told him zed i left your stuff in a
shulker box you can keep the box and
also i didn't loot it thanks i guess
so i got i got i got zeddaff's head and
he got he got a free shulker box so
i think i think he came out pretty good
on that i still got the tag only person
who has signed up currently to tag is
zombie clio
so just got to stay away from her you
know what i'm out i'm out i got some i
got work to do on my base let's get out
of here
my heart is going seriously that's it's
stressful i don't i'm not sure i'm into
this pvp thing but we did just have a
very very successful start to that game
oh okay now that that that bit of very
quick action is out of the way
i have
been wanting to start this since last
episode and i think it's about time we
really really got going so let's grab
our dirt
let's grab our cam account
and let's grab some funky music and get
going
on turning this into a real base
[Music]
now i've had to stop the time lapse
because basically if i'm really getting
into this i'm i'm honestly i just want
to continue building this but there's
two problems one i'm running out of
resources
and two and if i don't stop this video
won't be done for at least four days
because i'm like six hours into this
build and that's all that i've managed
to do so i'm gonna have to just hold for
a second because i'm also starting to
get a little bit paranoid i have got
nine tag points on the tab list at the
moment and i know that there are people
that are watching me i can feel their
eyes in the jungle somewhere so what i'm
going to do is i'm going to quickly
check i need to know who i'm looking out
for so i need to make a very quick trip
to the shopping district to see who's
signed up you must know your enemy
one of them's right here
is he afk let's just push him off the
edge
how did he not notice
all right so we got green cleo beef
iskall scar gevin false hypnotized club
iskall's on the list better steer clear
the shopping district is whoa
starting to fill up quite a lot
and then there's just this gigantic
thing so pretty much everyone that's
online is getting involved in tag at the
moment
i've got i've got rockets on standby not
a lot of people just yet but these are
the people we need to look out for you
know what let's just let's just get out
of here this guy this guy looks like
he's eyeing me up now that a few people
have signed up i feel like we need to we
need to do exactly what we did in season
six with the tag game we need a panic
room
somewhere we can go to ensure our safety
and since i'm going to be working around
here i think i need my panic room to be
really accessible somewhere around here
now i need this to just look as
non-suspicious as possible now i have an
idea this is gonna be all about trying
to fool people into thinking that i'm
trying to hide okay so what i'll do
is i'll come in here and i'll seal up
behind me and then they'll think that
i'm trying to hide and they'll know
where i am i'll like unintentionally
uncrouch
and then we'll see what we're gonna do
we're gonna kill them
with some full damage
oh
i almost
almost made a default minecraft sound
there i thought i got all the caves
around here but clearly not free iron
i'm always in need of iron at the moment
well it's good to know that i've got a
spider spawner directly under my mansion
oh my goodness seriously
i've got a lot of lighting up work to do
yeah that's that's an insane amount of
caves that i've got to light up
oh my goodness gracious me i think this
is a job for another time for the time
being i think we're just gonna pretend
that this doesn't exist okay that's
literally all the way down to bedrock
bedrock should be just around here
okay so this is
the deepest it can go so the amount of
fall damage here should be
significant i think that is an easy
death the idea is very very simple i'm
gonna get whoever chases me to fall down
here thinking it's safe the second that
they get
as soon as i see them traveling i'm just
going to remove the water the safety
water that they think will be there and
boof dead okay so then i just need to
wake away out i mean this is like this
is the oldest trick in the book but
i i mean it's what i can make in a pinch
and i'm pretty sure people will be after
me very very soon so i just need a quick
way out and then we're good to go
literally just this
so tiny amount of redstone i walk up i
go like this there should be water in
the bottom and then i just hop down
it'll close behind me
please don't die and if all else fails
and of course if all else fails i can
always just fly up the escape hatch and
leave them behind
i think i still retain the best flyer on
the server so i can probably get away
with it i mean how have i got myself
into this situation
i keep a water bucket on me really
really simple so
here's the theory okay
so here's the theory
if i get chased
of course if i'm chased somewhere else
this is going to be useless but at least
if i'm around my base i should have the
opportunity to get out fly
run to the panic room i then fly in here
i then pretend like i'm hiding and then
crouch maybe un crouch go like this fall
down in here
they should follow i'll i'll make them
see me fall down
they go like that i wait for them i wait
for them to start falling just at the
right second i remove the water
boom
panic room done and then i can fly out
to safety
get rid of this
and job done
so even if they did this they would see
that there's water at the bottom i mean
they might be a bit suspicious but i'll
make it look like this is i'll make it
look like this really isn't my panic
room i'll make it look like my panic
room is actually down there
at least that's the theory anyway
well i'm not sure if this is entirely
going to work
but either way that's a very quick 10
minute
protection for me in case someone comes
after me i might need to make a slightly
better panic room for when other people
come for me
hello hello hello in my comments
it was a resounding please keep the
resource pack on so that is exactly what
we're going to do we're going to
continue trading with these guys
and i do actually need to get rid of
some of the extra villagers the server
is struggling a little bit on the lag
front
so i do need to get rid of the extra
golems and some of the extra villages
that i don't need
i'm sure they'll forgive me i am
actually wondering though if i am able
to turn this into some kind of iron farm
because spawning a lot of golems
i'm an expert on these now
oh no
sorry
just don't hello walk in front of me
there we go
now i'm safe to get rid of some of the
uh
some of the ones that are not i don't
think so ew no
no i'm sorry
hello hello
and also getting rid of the ones that
aren't useful getting rid of these is
not only going to help with lag it's
also
sorry
hello i have died
it's also going to stop with the the
insane amount of hello that i get
there we go that's a bit better already
there we go cleared up some of that i do
need to organize these a little bit
better than just letting them loose in
the greenhouse
even though i've had to slow down on the
base build
i am going to be working on this
literally all the time i'm a little bit
like obsessed with it i just want to get
it finished or at least get the front of
it finished so it starts looking like a
proper base you can see what i meant
about working with diagonals it's been a
really difficult challenge making
triangles with this shape and it doesn't
look it doesn't look perfect but from a
distance and if you don't look too
closely looks absolutely fine but there
are many other jobs that need doing for
example this creeper farm although it
works
and i keep having to turn it off because
scar keeps leaving it on
it needs it needs decorating it is just
really really ugly
so i want to kind of keep the same
thematic thing over here that scar has
with these uh these pillars this sort of
like monolith type thing so that's what
we're gonna do here and the great news
about that is it only costs stone which
i have plenty of so let's uh kick off
another little quick build time lapse to
get this
somewhat decorated we're gonna have to
move this beacon maybe the beacon can go
in the middle
oh that would look absolutely amazing i
think everything's coming together let's
go
[Music]
i messaged scar and he said he would
love to decorate this in his stream that
he's doing later today so we kind of had
a a mutual agreement here that i would
make this shape which took me it took me
a little while and he's going to
decorate it somehow so i'm excited to
see what he's going to do but i think
this actually has come out really really
nicely
obviously we still got a bit of an ugly
hole in the middle here but this sort of
monolith
structure with the beacon dead center i
think this actually looks really cool
it's it definitely in keeping with
this thing over here the entrance to the
mines and it synergizes with his portal
build over here so this this area is
starting to get really nicely developed
and i think it fits as well as like a
centerpiece because look i can see
i don't want to spoil it because i don't
i don't know how much of this has
already been shown but i can see the
startings of mumbo's base over there
my base is here if only i'd made my base
slightly this way because then we'd
actually be in line
but either way it actually makes a
really nice focal point i don't know
where scar's gonna make his base but if
he's over there or over there ah yeah
this could be like the central hub of
everything
now while i was time lapsing scar said
that there was some free cake for me
and if that's not suspicious as he scar
is this really the best free cake
scar about to do me with the free cake
he he thinks he's gonna get me with that
come on scar i know you want this tag i
saw that you were you were signed up for
it
[Laughter]
and um i can't help but feel
there's been a uh
yeah there's been a failed attempt here
so i think
hmm
uh i wonder what's gonna happen if i eat
the cake scar
probably something like this
i wonder if i can do a flyby hopefully i
won't die because if i die i think it's
only like right if i die while i'm
holding the tag and i die to a trap
i think i should really like you know
give them the tag because they got me
even if he's not online i think that's
like a jet that's a that's a gentleman
gentleman's thing to do so
if somehow this gets me
then uh actually you know what we're not
even gonna risk we're never gonna risk a
flyby we're just gonna play this safe
this is season seven green does redstone
we're gonna remote detonate
he's just logged in hope he doesn't see
this
did you re i mean if he's a if he's
really smart and he's put like the tnt
over here then i mean kudos to him but
like
come on scar
come on did you did you really think did
you really think i was gonna fall for
that one man we've made a mess here now
scott we're gonna have to we're gonna
have to fix this up
[Laughter]
nice try guy
the attempts are gonna come in i think
scar knows that in i think in a pvp
fight he knows he's not gonna win
so i
i think that's what i think that's why
he's gone for a trap
free cake
but i did notice something my sword
has absolutely
no sharpness on it meaning it's really
really underpowered if someone came for
me i would lose a fight simply because
my enchantments are not good
so i need some more levels on me
it should this all should fill up and
then i can take this this might take a
little while to fill up actually while
that's ticking away i might continue
working on the base because this is
coming along nicely i bought up all of
the dark prismarine that was in the
shopping district and it's not going to
be enough for even a couple of layers
maybe not even one layer around the base
i'm going to need so much dark
prismarine so this is going to be a
long-term issue one thing i never
thought i'd run out of is andersite but
i am running very very close to empty on
it i may have to take up scar on his uh
challenge his mining challenge simply
because
i don't think i have enough
i don't think i have enough but my
goodness this is going well
you know these sheep have been they've
been doing some work i don't think i'm
actually going to need that much
oh no no let's go
let's go i'm going to give him oh dear
okay panic green panicking panic room
that's what he's there for where is he
where is he
where's he going i need to make sure
he's chasing me oh he's there he's there
he's there he's there he's there run run
run run run run run run run run run run
down down down down down
oh my goodness
oh my god that was so clutch
oh no
please please tell me you were off going
after the tag
when will you learn
i better give him his stuff back
oh i better give him his stuff back but
i'm kind of scared to give him his stuff
back because he's
oh this panic room worked so well
oh my goodness gracious me
well now i need a new panic room because
he now knows what this is all about oh
my goodness i can't believe that worked
it's a shame i couldn't get his
minecraft mob head though for the
headhunt now where's his scales portal
in theory he shouldn't have any gear
because i've got i've got all his gear
stress this must be a scouse i'm only
guessing though yep there we go
hello
how do i get out
right that should be all of his stuff
right here
i can't open these okay it was just it
was just a bug then i just i re-logged
and it seems to be working okay is there
anything else of uh iskals here i don't
i feel like i shouldn't shouldn't stick
around here too much do you have a bow
if he had a bow it's gone i think that
might have been his bow okay right i
think that's his stuff oh he's hit
uh your stuff's here oh cup cup what the
heck
seriously if only someone hadn't have
stolen his door right if he starts
putting his if he starts putting his
stuff on we're going for him there he is
he's
no no no no
no no no no no no no bad badass gal i'm
i'm keeping the head though i need that
i'm getting out of here i'm getting out
of here i'm getting out of here before i
die you saw it you guys saw it he was
gearing up he was getting up to get me
i'm flying home i don't want anything to
do with this anymore i'm keeping your
pumpkin pie too to be honest it serves
him right i served him right
i can't trust him okay let's go and put
this iskall head onto the scoreboard and
the pvp head goes to me who got this one
corrales pvp tier one all right
wait a minute
oh my goodness people have been
busy oh there's a scoreboard cub has 400
i'm in fifth place
i'm in fifth place i
i thought i was doing well
300 234
i think i might tap out
to be honest
i might put all my energy in trying to
stay with the tag because i'm not sure i
can compete with that unless i do
something extremely cheesy
we have once again held on to tag to
electric boogaloo we have held onto it
for exactly an entire episode because
unfortunately it's that time again and
i'm sorry
it is all we have time for in today's
episode we have got a lot done though
look at this the building of this thing
that scar is now currently working on we
have made some progress on the base and
we have successfully held on to tag to
electric boogaloo we will need to review
our
secret
panic room because now that has been
yeah that's been blasted and i have a
feeling
look listen to me it's girl he's gonna
be back and he's just he's just gonna
play it safer
i am so surprised i didn't see him i saw
him like at the corner of my eye
freaked me out a little bit
okay so thank you very very much for
watching the start of this season has
been absolutely insane
i cannot thank you enough
i will see you in the next episode good
bye